<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">FromProm2Marriage</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="prom_at_chat">Prom at CHAT</string>
    <string name="prom_and_friendship">Prom and Friendship</string>
    <string name="about_friendship">
         \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 A friend is someone who gives you total freedom to be yourself.
        \nJim Morrison\n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        A friend is one that knows you as you are, 
        understands where you have been, 
        accepts what you have become,  
        and still, gently allows you to grow. 
        \nWilliam Shakespeare    \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Yesterday is history, 
        tomorrow is a mystery, 
        today is a gift of God, which is why we call it the present. 
        \nBil Keane \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        A true friend is someone who thinks that you are a good egg 
        even though he knows that you are slightly cracked. 
        \nBernard Meltzer \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        I think if I\'ve learned anything about friendship, 
        it\'s to hang in, stay connected, fight for them, 
        and let them fight for you. Don\'t walk away, don\'t be distracted, 
        don\'t be too busy or tired, don\'t take them for granted.
        Friends are part of the glue that holds life and faith together. 
        Powerful stuff. 
        \nJon Katz \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Well, it seems to me that the best relationships - the ones that last -
         are frequently the ones that are rooted in friendship. 
         You know, one day you look at the person and you see something more 
         than you did the night before. Like a switch has been flicked somewhere. 
         And the person who was just a friend is \u002E\u002E\u002E suddenly 
         the only person you can ever imagine yourself with. 
         \nGillian Anderson           
        </string>
    <string name="atfter_marriage">atfter marriage</string>
    <string name="about_love">\u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        Love is composed of a single soul inhabiting two bodies.
        \nAristotle \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Love is that condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own.
        \nRobert Heinlein \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Life is a flower of which love is the honey.
        \nVictor Hugo \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        We\'re all a little weird, and life\'s a little weird.
         And when we find someone whose weirdness is compatible with ours, 
         we join up with them and fall in mutual weirdness and call it love.
         \nDr. Seuss \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
         
         Love is something sent from Heaven to worry the Hell out of you.
         \nDolly Parton \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Love is but the discovery of ourselves in others, and the delight in the recognition.
        \nAlexander Smith \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0 
        
        There is no remedy for love but to love more.
        \nThoreau \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        Seize the moments of happiness, love and be loved! 
        That is the only reality in the world, all else is folly.
        \nLeo Tolstoy \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0
        
        You\'ve gotta dance like there\'s nobody watching,
Love like you\'ll never be hurt,
Sing like there\'s nobody listening,
And live like it\'s heaven on earth. 
\nWilliam W. Purkey \n \u00A0\u00A0\u00A0

Only once in your life, 
I truly believe, you find someone who can completely turn your world around. 
You tell them things that you’ve never shared with another soul and 
they absorb everything you say and actually want to hear more. 
You share hopes for the future, dreams that will never come true, goals that were never achieved and the many disappointments life has thrown at you. When something wonderful happens, 
you can’t wait to tell them about it, 
knowing they will share in your excitement.
They are not embarrassed to cry with you when you are hurting or laugh with you when you make a
 fool of yourself.
  Never do they hurt your feelings or make you feel like you are not good enough, 
  but rather they build you up and show you the things about yourself that make you special and
   even beautiful. There is never any pressure, jealousy or competition but only a quiet 
   calmness when they are around. You can be yourself and not worry about what they will think 
   of you because they love you for who you are.
    The things that seem insignificant to most people such as a note, 
    song or walk become invaluable treasures kept safe in your heart to cherish forever. 
    Memories of your childhood come back and are so clear and vivid it’s like being young again.
     Colours seem brighter and more brilliant. 
     Laughter seems part of daily life where before it was infrequent or didn’t exist at all. 
     A phone call or two during the day helps to get you through a long day’s work and always 
     brings a smile to your face. In their presence, 
     there’s no need for continuous conversation, 
     but you find you’re quite content in just having them nearby.
      Things that never interested you before become fascinating because you know they are 
      important to this person who is so special to you. You think of this person on every occasion 
      and in everything you do. Simple things bring them to mind like a pale blue sky, gentle wind or
       even a storm cloud on the horizon. You open your heart knowing that there’s a chance it may 
       be broken one day and in opening your heart, you experience a love and joy that you never
        dreamed possible. You find that being vulnerable is the only way to allow your heart to feel
         true pleasure that’s so real it scares you. You find strength in knowing you
          have a true friend and possibly a soul mate who will remain loyal to the end.
           Life seems completely different, exciting and worthwhile. Your only hope and security is
            in knowing that they are a part of your life. 
\nBob Marley \n

        
        </string>
    <string name="marriage_and_love">Marriage and Love</string>

</resources>
